import albania from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/al.svg";
import andorra from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/ad.svg";
import austria from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/at.svg";
import belarus from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/by.svg";
import belgium from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/be.svg";
import bosniaAndHerzegovina from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/ba.svg";
import bulgaria from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/bg.svg";
import croatia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/hr.svg";
import czechia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/cz.svg";
import cyprus from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/cy.svg";
import denmark from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/dk.svg";

/*
import estonia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/estonia.svg";
import finland from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/finland.svg";
import france from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/france.svg";
import germany from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/germany.svg";
import greece from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/greece.svg";
import hungary from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/hungary.svg";
import iceland from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/iceland.svg";
import ireland from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/ireland.svg";
import italy from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/italy.svg";
import kosovo from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/kosovo.svg";
import latvia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/latvia.svg";
import liechtenstein from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/liechtenstein.svg";
import lithuania from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/lithuania.svg";
import luxembourg from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/luxembourg.svg";
import malta from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/malta.svg";
import moldova from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/moldova.svg";
import monaco from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/monaco.svg";
import montenegro from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/montenegro.svg";
import netherlands from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/netherlands.svg";
import northMacedonia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/north-macedonia.svg";
import norway from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/norway.svg";
import poland from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/poland.svg";
import portugal from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/portugal.svg";
import romania from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/romania.svg";
import russia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/russia.svg";
import sanMarino from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/san-marino.svg";
import serbia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/serbia.svg";
import slovakia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/slovakia.svg";
import slovenia from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/slovenia.svg";
import spain from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/spain.svg";
import sweden from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/sweden.svg";
import switzerland from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/switzerland.svg";
import unitedKingdom from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/united-kingdom.svg";
import vaticanCity from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/vatican-city.svg";
import ukraine from "Catalog/en/country-outline/europe/img/ukraine.svg";
*/


// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/gb.svg",


  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: [],
}



export var cards = {
  "al": {
    image: albania,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Albania"
  },
  "ad": {
    image: andorra,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Andorra"
  },
  "at": {
    image: austria,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Austria"
  },
  "by": {
    image: belarus,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Belarus"
  },
  "be": {
    image: belgium,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Belgium"
  },
  "ba": {
    image: bosniaAndHerzegovina,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Bosnia And Herzegovina"
  },
  "bg": {
    image: bulgaria,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Bulgaria"
  },  
  "hr": {
    image: croatia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Croatia"
  },
  "cz": {
    image: czechia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Czechia"
  },
  "cy": {
    image: cyprus,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Cyprus"
  },
  "dk": {
    image: denmark,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Denmark"
  },
  /*
  "ee": {
    image: estonia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Estonia"
  },
  "fi": {
    image: finland,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Finland"
  },
  "fr": {
    image: france,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "France"
  },
  "de": {
    image: germany,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Germany"
  },
  "gr": {
    image: greece,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Greece"
  },
  "hu": {
    image: hungary,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Hungary"
  },
  "is": {
    image: iceland,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Iceland"
  },
  "ie": {
    image: ireland,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Ireland"
  },
  "it": {
    image: italy,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Italy"
  },
  "xk": {
    image: kosovo,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Kosovo"
  },
  "lv": {
    image: latvia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Latvia"
  },
  "li": {
    image: liechtenstein,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Liechtenstein"
  },
  "lt": {
    image: lithuania,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Lithuania"
  },
  "lu": {
    image: luxembourg,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Luxembourg"
  },
  "mt": {
    image: malta,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Malta"
  },
  "md": {
    image: moldova,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Moldova"
  },
  "mc": {
    image: monaco,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Monaco"
  },
  "me": {
    image: montenegro,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Montenegro"
  },
  "nl": {
    image: netherlands,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Netherlands"
  },
  "mk": {
    image: northMacedonia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "North Macedonia"
  },
  "no": {
    image: norway,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Norway"
  },
  "pl": {
    image: poland,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Poland"
  },
  "pt": {
    image: portugal,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Portugal"
  },
  "ro": {
    image: romania,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Romania"
  },
  "ru": {
    image: russia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Russia"
  },
  "sm": {
    image: sanMarino,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "San Marino"
  },
  "rs": {
    image: serbia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Serbia"
  },
  "sk": {
    image: slovakia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Slovakia"
  },
  "si": {
    image: slovenia,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Slovenia"
  },
  "es": {
    image: spain,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Spain"
  },
  "se": {
    image: sweden,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Sweden"
  },
  "ch": {
    image: switzerland,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Switzerland"
  },
  "gb": {
    image: unitedKingdom,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "United Kingdom"
  },
  "va": {
    image: vaticanCity,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Vatican City"
  },
  "ua": {
    image: ukraine,
    type: 'inner',
    prompt: "What country is this?",
    answer: "Ukraine"
  },
  */
};